richxrong.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy

####  Privacy Policy 

Our tough security and privacy policy keeps your trusted information safe and private. Information can only be accessed by staff to assist you, access is only available to third parties if you have given written permission or is to assist in criminal investigations. richxrong.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site and we guarantee that we will not sell, share, or rent your information to any outside parties.

####  Collecting information 

By using richxrong.com you authorize us to collect, store and use your personal information to  
. Process your orders;  
. Process your membership registration;  
. Assist you in a customer service enquiries;  
. Send you promotional material;  
. Identify you on our forums;  
. Assist in calculating commissions for; affiliate, dropship, wholesale or review programs;  
. Verify your identity with our payment partners.

####  What information do we collect and store? 

Registered email/ password /nickname/ IP address/ the date and time/ browser and operating system/ the URL you requested/ your PayPal email / your PayPal shipping address and other information. Some examples of why we need this information include assisting in pre orders, delivery, payment verification, promotions and newsletters, statistics on website use to aid in improving our customer experience and offering the most popular products. To contact you about sales, special offers and new site features, unless you have elected not to receive promotional communications in connection with this website. If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, you can click the unsubscribe link.

 **Note** : No one other than yourself can access your password, including our staff.

####  How do we collect the information? 

1\. When you browse our website, we may collect your IP address, browser, operating system, and the URL you request.  
2\. When you order on our website, we may collect the registered email, password, nickname, IP address, the date and time, browser and operating system, the URL you request, your PayPal email and your PayPal shipping address.  
3\. If we have a partnership with you, we may collect more information, for example, your phone number, your website, MSN, Facebook, your online URL for reviews and testimonials.

####  How do we store your personal information? 

We have a secure storage system for both offline and online information to ensure that your information is well protected. However it still remains important that you never share your username and password with any other person.

While we aim to store your personal information secure and private, we shall not be responsible for any breach of security caused by third parties, nor do we represent that richxrong.com is completely secure.

####  How do I access my stored information? 

You have the right to view, update and correct information stored by richxrong.com. To access your personal information login to your richxrong account and click my details or contact [[email protected]](http://www.richxrong.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)            

####  External Links 

Our website contains links to other external sites. Please be aware that richxrong.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

####  Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Customers are responsible for periodically checking the Privacy & Policy available on the website for changes. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage.

####  Questions or Concerns 

Questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the Contact Us link in the upper menu. Or through the following methods:                  

Contact  Us 

Email: [[email protected]](http://www.richxrong.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
